wmo.ch 2014-03-30

# World Meterological Organization (WMO) - Privacy

Privacy policy  |   
---|---  
Home >

## Privacy policy

To make sure your personal information remains confidential on the Internet, we are committed to provide the privacy policy for our online visitors. This privacy policy is to inform you of our online information practices and the choices available regarding the collection and use of your information. By accessing this site, information about the user, such as:

  * Internet protocol address
  * Browser or computer type
  * Number of links clicked within the site
  * State or country from which the site was accessed
  * Date and time of visit
  * Name of Internet service provider
  * Web page from which our site was linked
  * Web page being referenced
  * Pages viewed on the site
  * Specific searches conducted
  * Software used and the time spent on our site

may be stored on the servers of the WMO website. This information will not specifically identify the user. We may collect information during visits in order to understand your usage (website traffic analysis) and ensure that future content decisions reflect your needs. Information about users of the website and their usage is maintained in a secure environment. We respect the privacy and security of its users. We will never sell your e-mail address to any third party for any reason. 

We, however, assume no responsibility for the security of this information. The Web is not secure and any information entered in a Web form can be stolen from unscrupulous spammers who will “harvest” these records. We in no way aid these spammers or provide them with users’ e-mails. We do not participate in marketing campaigns. 

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your identity. For your protection, we may require additional levels of confirmation for some actions that may be initiated on this site.

The website employs a standard technology called cookies* to save user preferences of the website on your computer. No personally identifiable information would be collected and saved.  Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You can choose to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the choice of rejecting or accepting the cookie. 

*Like many websites today, we may employ a standard technology called cookies to collect information about how you use our site in order to provide you with a better experience by measuring which areas of our website of greatest interest or to remember you when you return to visit us. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You can choose to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the choice of rejecting or accepting the cookie.
